mollysdailykiss.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Molly's Daily Kiss

We strongly believe in the importance of keeping your personal information personal. We will never use your information for any use beyond that stated or the permissions you give us or as required by law.

Mollysdailykiss.com may collect, process and use your personal data. We will do so to contact you regarding the services you have requested and/or to offer services to you, and/or to provide the services you have requested. This includes comments and subscriptions .Mollysdailykiss.com may employ trusted third party specialists to process and use your data on our behalf in order to deliver content to you in a more efficient manner.

### IP Addresses and Server Logs

Mollysdailykiss.com website does record IP addresses and produces server logs – as all Web Servers do. This information is used solely for monitoring the volume of traffic the site receives and measuring the number of readers. We do not use the information for tracking the activities of specific visitors to the site. IP addresses are also stored by the WordPress CMS software when you comment.

### Cookies

Mollysdailykiss.com site sets cookies in order to enable certain user features.

### Analytics

Mollysdailykiss.com also uses Google Analytics to help us expand our reach on the internet to grow our traffic, we anonymize all IP address information. Here is the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

### Email and Online Forms

Readers who choose to subscribe to our newsletter, or complete any of our online forms, may be asked to supply personal data. If they choose to do so, that information is recorded and used for broad demographic information.

Mollysdailykiss.com will never use your data for anything beyond the reason stated and the permissions you grant us. To alter the emails which you receive from us, including unsubscribing from all email communications, please [visit this page](https://mollysdailykiss.com/contact-me/). Make sure that you enter exactly the same e-mail address as you used to sign up.

### Competitions

Readers who enter Mollysdailykiss.com competitions will be asked for some personal information, but only to allow us to judge the validity of their applications and to contact them should they be declared a competition winner.

If permission is granted, this information may be used to send occasional emails from Mollysdailykiss.com. This will only ever be provided to readers that have specifically given us permission to use their information in this way.

Mollysdailykiss.com will never use your data for anything beyond the reason stated and the permissions you grant us.

### Publishing

We reserve the right to publish comments made on the Mollysdailykiss.com website. The website requires an email address to comment, but we will never publish your email address. You may use any email address to comment. The WordPress software records the IP address of your device when you comment, but that IP address is never published and will be removed from our system if you request to have all of your data removed.

### Our servers

Stressfree.host hosts the Mollysdailykiss.com website.

### Data Protection

Anyone who provides Mollysdailykiss.com with personal information is given the opportunity to manage how that information is used. This includes opting out of any services and restricting the use of that information. You can do that by visiting the links in our newsletter emails

### Accessing your Data

You have certain rights under the UK’s Data Protection Act 1998 (“DPA”). You can, for instance, ask in writing to be told what information we hold about you in our databases and how that information is being processed. Mollysdailykiss.com will provide you with all of the details that we hold about you, both online and offline, upon request, providing we are able to do so in compliance with our obligations under the DPA.

Mollysdailykiss.com request this information please use the contact details below.

### Changes to this Policy

As statutory and online requirements change so this policy document may change. Any changes will be highlighted across the site to ensure that all readers have the opportunity to respond to these changes.

### Contacting Molly’s Daily Kiss regarding your data

If you wish to contact Mollysdailykiss.com regarding any aspect of the Privacy Policy you should use the following [contact form](https://mollysdailykiss.com/contact-me/)
